hongkongairlines.com 2010-12-24

# Welcome to HONG KONG AIRLINES

Hong Kong Airlines Limited & Hong Kong Express Airways Limited ("Our Company") respects the privacy of the information provided by users and will endeavor to ensure that proper protection is given to such information.  
Our Company pledges to meet, and where possible exceed, internationally recognized standards of data privacy protection, in complying with the law of confidence and/or the requirements of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, whichever is applicable. In doing so, Our Company will ensure compliance by our staff with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality.

Corporate/Personal Information :  
When you use our web site, Our Company may request you to provide us with your corporate/personal data as may be required by Our Company from time to time. 

**Methods in Collecting Corporate/Personal Data :**

  1. The input of figures for all calculations; 
  2. Enquiry forms and information provided by you in your enquiry; 
  3. Messages by you in our web site; 
  4. Questionnaire submitted by you; 
  5. The email between you and Our Company; 
  6. Your activity record of our website; 
  7. Cookies files to store and track your information without your notice; 

Any other means as reasonably accessible to Our Company from time to time. 

**Purposes for Collection of Corporate/Personal Data :**

  1. To compile the general statistical database of our web site, for instance, number of browsers, time of visits, occupation and gender distribution of visitors and members. 
  2. The introduction or supply of suitable products and service in accordance with your interest and habits. 
  3. The delivery of products and service information requested by you. 
  4. The collection of identity documentation number for the purpose of verification. 
  5. To facilitate Our Company to verify and follow up any matters and questions (including but not limited to overdue payments) in respect of any account maintained by yourself with Our Company (and/or with any of Our Company's holding company, subsidiaries and associates). For this purpose, you hereby authorize Our Company to furnish, transfer and disclose all or any of your corporate/personal data to any party(ies) to follow up and settle the said matters and questions. 
  6. To facilitate the implementation of any activities or services to be co-organized by Our Company and our business partners. 

To facilitate Our Company to design and provide you with better and more tailored-made services and to facilitate Our Company to develop and promote the business of Our Company. 

**Guidelines for disclosure of Corporate/ Personal Data to Third Parties :**

  1. The corporate/personal data collected by Our Company, Our Company's holding company, subsidiaries and associates would be exchanged when required to perform any of the aforesaid purposes for collection of corporate/personal data and other matters and arrangements which can facilitate the said performance; 
  2. The companies and contractors who provide services to Our Company may obtain corporate/personal data collected by Our Company to perform any of the aforesaid purposes for collection of corporate/personal data and other matters and arrangements which can facilitate the said performance. These data will only be protected by their own corporate/personal data (protection of privacy) rules. However, Our Company will use our best endeavor to keep the collected corporate/personal data confidential. 
  3. When you activate any link and access to websites operated by others from Our Company's website, any of your corporate/personal data released and/or obtained by others at the said other link and websites will not be under the protection of our Privacy Policy. 
  4. Clients' identifiable information will not be disclosed to our advertisers. But, Our Company will deliver notice and email to targeted advertising audience to provide statistical data of our web site to them. 
  5. In activities or services co-organized by Our Company and our business partners, shared information will include the corporate/personal records which are necessary for the implementation of such activities and services. 

To perform any of the aforesaid purposes for collection of corporate/personal data and other matters and arrangements which can facilitate the said performance and/or to facilitate any due diligence exercise in respect of any potential acquisition/merger transaction(s) involving Our Company, Our Company is entitled to furnish, transfer and disclose any of your corporate/personal data obtained as aforesaid to any person under a duty of confidentiality to Our Company. Our Company will use our best endeavor to keep the collected corporate/personal data confidential. 

**Other Information Collectors**  
Except as otherwise stated, this Privacy Policy governs and addresses only the use and disclosure of the information we collect from you. As far as the information that you disclose to other parties, including but not limited to the advertisers, business partners and our strategic alliances on our system or other sites throughout the Internet, is concerned, different rules and policies shall apply to their respective use or disclosure of your information. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they have their own privacy customs and policies. Since Our Company and/or its other related companies do not have control of the privacy policies of third parties, your information disclosed to them is subject to their privacy customs and policies. It is thus advisable for you to ensure that you understand the effect of the privacy customs and policies of other third parties before you disclose your corporate/personal information to them.  
While we strive to protect your corporate/personal information, Our Company and/or its other related companies cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In addition, third party Internet sites and other third party's services accessible through our sites or other parties which are collecting data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, etc., have separate and independent privacy and data collection practices. Under no circumstances should Our Company and/or its other related companies be held responsible and liable for these other and independent policies, actions and/or any loss, damages and claim that you may suffer in relation thereto. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

Our Company reserves the right to amend our Privacy Policy to enable your corporate/personal data to be fully protected.
